mn.co 2018-05-23

# Privacy Policy

###### Last updated: November 5, 2017

* * *

### Welcome to Mighty Networks!

All visitors to our Service (“Visitors”) who register with the Service and join a Mighty Network are Members or Hosts. Hosts are the organizers of Mighty Networks. Members register and participate in Mighty Networks. Hosts decide who can join their Mighty Network and whether they choose to run advertising or paid Member subscriptions on their Mighty Network. This Privacy Policy describes how we, Mighty Software, Inc., obtain and use information about you and your visits to our website at mightynetworks.com and your participation in a Mighty Network. To offer the personalized experience of a Mighty Network, we collect personal information about you (“Personal Data”). This policy describes how we collect, use, and share your Personal Data with your Host and other Members in connection with your use of the Service. By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you agree to this Privacy Policy. Unless defined here, capitalized words have the same meaning as in the Mighty Networks [Terms of Use](https://mightynetworks.com/terms_of_use), which this Privacy Policy is part of. 

### I. Information we collect and how we use it

When you interact with us through the Service, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you (collectively, “Data”): 

  * We collect Personal Data when you share it voluntarily.
  * We collect anonymous information automatically.
  * We and your Hosts use both your Personal Data and anonymous information to understand how you and other Members are using Mighty Networks, provide and improve the Service, and to inform you about products and services that may be of interest to you.
  * Data does not include Your Content or User Generated Content. As we explain in our Terms of Use, you (and the people you license Your Content from) keep complete ownership of all Your Content. By posting Your Content on the Service, you grant us a license to use it, but you and your licensors still own it.

### A. Personal data you provide directly

Some Personal Data is considered “personally identifiable information” or “PII.” An example is your name. Not all Personal Data is PII. An example of Personal Data that is not PII is your profession. We store and use your Personal Data together with an ID we assign each time you join a new Mighty Network. We assign you one ID per Mighty Network to ensure you have a personalized experience in each one.

**Name and Email Address.** When you register as a Host or Member of a Mighty Network, we ask you for your real name and your email address. Both we and the Host of the Mighty Network receive access to this information and use it to communicate with you about the Service. In addition, we and your Host may use this address to email you about products or services believed to be of interest to you. 

**Social Media Profiles.** You can also register with your Facebook or LinkedIn account. When you register this way, you give us permission to access your Facebook or LinkedIn profile and photo. Your profile and photo will become part of your Mighty Network profile. See below for more information on Integrated Services like Facebook and LinkedIn. 

**Profiles and Topics.** When you join a Mighty Network, you may be prompted to add a profile, including a short bio, and to choose topics to follow (“Topics”). From this information, Mighty Networks personalizes your experience in each Mighty Network. 

**Your Location.** We may ask you for your location so that we can facilitate interactions with other Members in your geographic area. In addition, our mobile app may collect your GPS location information. If you enable location features, or do not disable GPS on your mobile device, other Members may be able to see your location. 

**Other Personal Data You Provide Directly.** You may also provide us Personal Data when you use certain features of the Service, contact us with inquiries, or respond to one of our surveys. 

### B. Information we collect automatically

You have the option of registering using an Integrated Service, such as Facebook. If you choose to do this, your profile picture and other Personal Data in your profile on the Integrated Service will become part of your profile on Mighty Networks. Please see the section below on Integrated Services for more detail.

**Information About Your Use of the Service.** Our servers automatically record your visits to the Service. Like all other website and mobile app servers, ours compiles a log that records the date, time, browser (i.e., Firefox), device type (i.e., iPhone), operating system (i.e. Android), and originating IP address of each page request. 

We use cookies to collect the following information about your visit to our website Service: which website or ad you visited right before ours, which pages you visited on our Service, and how much time you spent on each section of our Service. We may also collect other data about your visit, such as search requests and results. We use this information to track usage of our Service, to measure the number of unique visitors to the different sections of our Service, to understand how Members find and join Mighty Networks, and to help us make our Service more valuable to every Host and Member. The use of this information is called “analytics.” Often information used for analytics is aggregated. 

Our mobile applications on iOS (Apple) and Android (Google) have to interact with our servers. We assign your device a token so that you do not have to log in every time you use the Service via our apps. 

You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some of our Service features may not function properly without cookies. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. We recommend that you leave cookies enabled so that we can offer you the best experience. For more information about cookies visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

**Information About Your Location.** From your IP address, we can tell generally where you are when you are accessing our Service, i.e., which city. We start by choosing a location for you based on the IP address of your Internet connection. You can update or remove this location at anytime. 

### C. Information third parties collect automatically

**Third-Party Cookies for Site Use Analysis.** We use third parties such as Google to help us analyze how people are using our Service. We also use the Google Analytics service to provide us with demographic data about our Hosts and Members, such as age and gender, on an anonymous basis. Google uses a cookie that can be recognized by Google or its affiliate DoubleClick when you visit other websites. 

**Third-Party Cookies Used to Target Ads to You When You Use the Service or are on Other Websites.** “Beacons” are transparent pixel images that are used in collecting information about website usage across websites and over time. We may work with other companies who use their cookies or beacons to target Mighty Networks or Host ads to you when you visit other websites. You may also see third party ads on our Service that are targeted to you based on the subject matter of your Mighty Network. Finally, you may see ads on our Service based on your prior visits to other websites, or you may see ads on third party websites based on your prior visits to our website Service. This is called online behavioral advertising (“OBA”), because you receive ads based on your prior online behavior. We do not have access to these cookies; it is third parties who engage in OBA. 

### II. Our disclosure of your Personal Data and other information

We consider personalizing your Mighty Networks experience an important part of our Service. We want you to understand what Personal Data gets shared with your Hosts, other Members of your Mighty Networks, other Hosts or Members of our Service, and other third parties as part of the Service. If you are not comfortable with this type of sharing, don’t use our Service.

### A. Personal data shared within the Service

**Your Host.** Your Host, or Hosts if are there more than one, will have access to your name, email address, and all personal or contact information that you provide when you register for a Mighty Network. In order to facilitate Member engagement, our Host will also have access to Data regarding your usage activity, in both aggregated and personally identifiable forms. For example, Hosts will be able to see aggregated Member activity within a Mighty Network, as well as specific information like how many people cheered in response to a comment you made. Your Host also will be able to associate Your Content, and any personal information it contains, with your contact information. Your Hosts may communicate with you outside of the Service about the Mighty Network or relevant topics of interest to you, and may retain your personal information after you leave the Mighty Network. You should only join a Mighty Network if you are comfortable sharing your personal information with the Hosts. 

**Searching and Messaging by Others.** Visitors to our Service may be able to search for you by your name and location if you are a Member of a Mighty Network. Members of your Mighty Network can search for you by location, Topics, or other personal information so that they may message you within the Mighty Network. Whether your information is available to other Visitors and Members way depends on whether the Mighty Network is Public, Private, or Secret. 

**Public, Private, and Secret Mighty Networks.** A Host can select whether to make a Mighty Network Public, Private, or Secret. In the case of Public Mighty Network, all Visitors (including Hosts and Members) can see your name and photo (“Profile”), as well as Your Content and activity. Unless your Host specifies otherwise, in a Public Mighty Network, search engines like Google index all public activity, including Profiles. In a Private Mighty Network, only Hosts and other Members can see Profiles, Your Content, and activity. For a Private Mighty Network, any Visitor can find the Mighty Network, but cannot enter without an invitation or membership request approval. In the case of a Secret Mighty Network, only Hosts or other Members of that Mighty Network can see Profiles, Your Content, and activity. Only Members directly invited can find a Secret Mighty Network. It is not available to search engines. 

**Personal Information Included in Your Content.** If you include personal information in Your Content, it will be displayed to other Members based on the privacy levels defined above. 

### B. Personal data shared with certain third parties

**Integrated Services.** We may share your information with the operators of any Integrated Services (as defined below), as more fully explained in the sections below entitled “Integrated Services.” 

**Business Transfers.** As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets. 

**Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties.** Mighty Software, Inc., like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases, and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information they need to perform their specific function. 

**Legal Requirements.** We may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Mighty Software, Inc., (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability. 

### C. Aggregated data shared

We disclose aggregated statistics, such as number of Hosts and Members, in order to describe our Service to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

### III. Your choices

### A. Join Mighty Networks and Hosts you trust

You get to decide the Mighty Networks you want to join. You also get to decide whether you trust your Host with the information sharing described in this policy.

### B. Public, Private, or Secret Mighty Network settings

A Host can choose to make a Mighty Network Public, Private, or Secret as described above.

### C. Adjust your notification settings

In your account settings, you can control the frequency, type, and mode of notifications. You can choose to be notified by email or mobile alerts, both, or neither. You can choose to turn on or off your notifications by type, such as cheers on your posts, and questions you can help answer.

### D. Opt out of email

If we send you emails about products or services that may interest you, each email will contain instructions permitting you to “opt-out” of receiving future marketing or other communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing or other communications, please contact us at [help@mightynetworks.com](mailto:help@mightynetworks.com). At times, we, together with Hosts, may also send co-branded emails to you. The opt-out instructions on these co-branded emails will state whether the opt-out applies solely to future emails from us, the Hosts, or both. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future marketing communications. Note however that as a Member of the Service you cannot opt-out of some administrative communications that are reasonably necessary to the Service, such as billing or service notifications. 

### E. Opt out of Google Analytics

To prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, [click here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) for instructions. 

### F. Opt out of Google behavioral advertising

To opt out of Google behavioral advertising, [click here](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en&sig=ACi0TChTOcTh0Zw8QqBdT-OCxwSpWwNT1J8JqZmRt7ctTZRDA5WnB7C5XGzaxHVmAcVuzxDUMaGmwnnuM2OTd9Ok7b3yLVXop1nNztHTA2RuWExj91hB3Rvsa6LlgnIcta-awwF2vWiSCobqQVwT-EeX9QxZ7GU1jSTs7h08u8BQLwdSH7562q9Ct2j68TucafNQLcODg_rn) to see your Google ad settings. 

### H. Opting out of tracking generally

We do not have access to, nor does this Privacy Policy govern, the use of cookies or other tracking technologies that may be placed on your computer, mobile phone, or other device by non-affiliated, third-party ad technology, ad servers, ad networks, or any other non-affiliated third parties. If you would like to learn more about OBA or to opt out of having this information used by companies that are part of the Network Advertising Initiative to deliver targeted ads, please visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

**1\. Deleting cookies** To manage or delete browser cookies, please see your browser's privacy settings. 

**2\. Do Not Track** Some browsers have a ‘do not track’ feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. These features are not yet uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to those signals. 

### IV. Account termination

You can leave one or more of your Mighty Networks, or close your account. As soon as you leave, we stop collecting Personal Data for that Mighty Network.

### V. Exclusions

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by Mighty Software, Inc. outside the Service, such as a telephone call. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Mighty Software, Inc. through the Service or through any other means, such as information posted to any public areas of the Service, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Mighty Software, Inc. shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, distribute, and exploit such Unsolicited Information without limitation or attribution. We respect your copyrights in Your Content, as outlined in our Terms of Use.

If your Host has an additional privacy policy covering the Host’s use of Personal Data, you should review it carefully, because it may be different than this Privacy Policy.

### VI. Disputes with Hosts or other Members

Mighty Networks cannot control the actions of Hosts or other Members; if you have a privacy-related dispute with a Host or another Member, you should contact that person directly. You should alert us [help@mightynetworks.com](mailto:help@mightynetworks.com)if you believe that a Host or another Member has violated our [Acceptable Use Policy](https://mightynetworks.com/acceptable_use_policy). 

### VII. Children

Mighty Networks does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not use the Service or submit any Personal Data through the Service. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to Mighty Networks through the Service, please contact us at [help@mightynetworks.com](mailto:help@mightynetworks.com) and we will look to delete that information from our databases. 

### VIII. Links to other web applications

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Service. The Service may contain links to other websites not operated or controlled by Mighty Software, Inc. (the “Third Party Sites”). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from the Service do not imply that Mighty Software, Inc. endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

### IX. Integrated services

One of the special features of the Service is that it allows you to enable various online third party services, such as social media and social networking services like Facebook and LinkedIn (each, an “Integrated Service”), to integrate directly into your Mighty Network. By directly integrating these services, we make your use of Mighty Networks richer and more personalized. To enable Integrated Services, we may ask you to authorize Mighty Networks to access the Integrated Services (or vice versa). When you add an Integrated Service account to a Mighty Network (or vice versa), your log-in information, Personal Data, non-personal data, location information, your content, your Mighty Network name, your Mighty Network location, your Mighty Network affiliation, profile photo, Facebook Connect ID, Profile (if you are integrating your Facebook account) and other relevant information may be passed through to, or received from, the Integrated Service in connection with your use of the Service. We may import, use, disclose, and retain such data and information to, among other things, customize and improve the Service for you and others. Note that Integrated Services may also import, use, and retain this information. You may be able to control how certain information is shared with us in your privacy settings within the Integrated Services. However, please remember that the manner in which Integrated Services collect, use, store, and disclose your information is governed solely by the policies of the third parties operating those Integrated Services, and we shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any Integrated Service that may be enabled within the Service.

From time to time, we may share your information with Integrated Services. This may happen when you first register with Mighty Networks, when you log into Mighty Networks from time to time, or in emails or other communications we may send you consistent with this Privacy Policy. We may from time to time share your Personal Data and anonymous data, your location information, your Mighty Network Membership, your Mighty Network URL, your location, and your use of certain features on Mighty Networks with Integrated Services to facilitate and enhance your use of the Integrated Services. Please keep in mind that services provided by Integrated Services are not provided by us and therefore your use of the Integrated Services will be governed by the Integrated Services' Terms of Use and other policies, and that the collection, use, and disclosure of information provided by you or us to Integrated Services is not governed by this Privacy Policy.

### X. Security

We take reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Service from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet, email, or other electronic transmission is ever fully secure or error free, so you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us in this way.

### XI. Changes to Mighty Networks' privacy policy

The Service and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for us to make changes to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Service after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

We have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any Integrated Service that may be enabled within the Service.

### XII. International visitors

Our Service operates in the U.S. If you provide Personal Data, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred by or on behalf of Mighty Software, Inc. from your current location to the offices and servers of Mighty Software, Inc. in the United States. You also understand that the U.S. may not provide the same level of protections as the laws of your country.

### XIII. California visitors

### A. California do-not-track disclosure requirements

We do not recognize or respond to browser-initiated Do-Not-Track signals, because the Internet industry is still working on uniform Do-Not-Track standards.

### B. Your California privacy rights

California law permits Visitors who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we have disclosed their personal information for direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the type of personal information disclosed to those parties. If you are a California resident and would like to request this information, please submit your request in an email to [info@mightynetworks.com](mailto:info@mightynetworks.com). 

### XIV. Access to information; contacting us

To keep your Personal Data accurate, current, and complete, please update your account settings or contact us at the email address below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via the Service.

Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about Mighty Networks’ Privacy Policy or the information practices of the Service. Our email address for privacy issues iss [info@mightynetworks.com](mailto:info@mightynetworks.com). Our postal address is Mighty Software, Inc., 127 Lytton Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94301.
